[Road to Success]
[星のように煌めく]
[Episode 31]
[第三十一話]
[Wang Fa]
[王法]
Chengye, you should sign it too.
文くんも名前を書き足して
D-Drunk.
酔っぱらい
Arrogant.
ツンデレめ
In the beginning,
最初
I was just a slacker who hadn't walked out of pain.
私はただの 立ち直れない干物人間だった
After the first meeting with you,
初めてのミーティング後
I was actually really happy.
実はすごく嬉しかったの
Because you all really sucked.
みんな本当にポンコツだったから
I thought...
もともと
after playing one round with you,
一回戦で負けたら
I could retire with success
お役御免になって
and continue to be a slacker.
また干物人間に戻れるって思ってた
Ms. Lin,
先生
you are really not sparing our feelings.
俺たちの顔を丸潰れにするね
-Yeah. -Exactly.
- そうだ
But I never thought
でも思いもしなかった
that I could actually
まさかみんなと
make it to the finals with you guys.
決勝まで行けるなんて
Everyone, stand up again.
全員 再度起立
I want...
私は
Once again, I want to grandly
改めて盛大に
thank
感謝したい
Mr. Win,
ミスターウィン
Coach Wang Fa.
王法 王コーチに
He provided our football team
彼がサッカー部に
with the most professional football training ground
宏景で最も専門的な練習場と
and hotel accommodation in Hongjing.
ホテルを提供してくれた
He
彼が
used the power of money
資金の力で
to support us in sprinting for the championship.
優勝への道を支えてくれたの
Just clapping is useless.
拍手だけじゃダメ
Let's prove it to him with practical actions.
実際の行動で彼に証明しよう
First bow.
一礼
-First bow. -Thank you, Coach.
- 一礼 - コーチありがとう
Second bow.
二礼
-Third bow. -All right. That's enough.
- 三礼 - わかった もういい
Don't interrupt me.
邪魔しないで
Fourth bow.
四礼
-Thank you, Coach.
コーチありがとう
-Fifth bow. -Go home.
- 五礼 - 帰るぞ
Listen to me.
コーチの言うこと聞け
You still have a match to play.
試合があるんだぞ
-Alright.
- ほら - はいはいはい
-Let's go.
行くぞ
-We're off, Coach.
- 行くぞ - じゃあね コーチ
Fifth bow.
五礼
-Stop. -Sixth bow.
- 五礼はない - 六礼
All right.
わかったから
-Don't hurt yourself. -Seventh bow.
- 怪我するなよ - 七礼
Let's go home.
帰るぞ
Fifteenth bow.
十五礼
With our level...
俺たちのレベルなら
Twentieth bow.
二十礼
Thirtieth bow.
三十礼
Fortieth bow.
四十礼
Fiftieth bow. Sixtieth bow.
五十礼 六十礼
A bit hungry.
腹減ったな
What to eat?
何食う？
[Fu Xinshu]
[付新書]
[Wen Cheng]
[文成]
[Wen Chengye]
[文成業]
Use this one.
これを使って
Why...
お前
why are you here?
なぜここに？
Ms. Lin is drunk.
林先生が酔ってて
No one locked the door.
鍵が開いてたんだ
You actually could have
正面から
just pushed the front door open and come in.
そのまま入って来られたのに
I...
私は
I forgot to take my stuff.
忘れ物を取りに
Really?
そう？
Do you want to sign it?
サインする？
[Wen Chengye] [Fu Xinshu]
[文成業][付新書]
[Wen Cheng]
[文成]
I'm very happy
とても嬉しい
that we can play football together again.
また一緒にサッカーできる
W-Whatever you say.
好きに言えば
Fu Xinshu. Wen Chengye.
付新書 文成業
We're home. Wait.
着いたわ 待って
Thank you for taking me home.
送ってくれてありがとう
Alright.
さあ
You've bowed over 100 times on the way.
ここまで百回以上お辞儀したぞ
Come on, take your shoes off.
ほら 靴を脱いで
That many?
そんなにしたの？
Yes.
したんだぞ
You counted?
数えたの？
I did.
数えた
I should go wash up.
顔を洗いに行ってくる
Can you do it yourself?
一人で大丈夫？
Yes.
大丈夫
Don't worry about me.
気にしないで
Take it easy.
気をつけて
Done washing.
洗ったわ
Time to sleep. Turn off the lights.
寝るわ 電気消して
Are you uncomfortable?
気分悪いか？
Here.
ほら
Drink some water.
水を飲んで
Get a good rest.
ゆっくり休め
Contact me anytime if you need anything.
何かあれば連絡して
Wang Fa.
王法
I took a shower,
なんで私がお風呂に入ったのに
but why do you smell even better than me?
あなたのほうがいい匂いなのよ
♪ I caught your eyes ♪
♪ 君のまなざしを見つけた ♪
♪ On the summer night ♪
♪ あの夏の夜に ♪
♪ Like stars that glow so bright ♪
♪ 眩しく輝く星のようだった ♪
♪ A spark in my heart ♪
♪ 胸に灯る小さな火は ♪
♪ Lost in a dream secretly ♪
♪ 夢の中へ そっと消えてゆく ♪
♪ With the evening breeze whispering in my ear ♪
♪ 夜風が耳元に 吹き寄せる告白 ♪
♪ Fireworks bloom across the sky ♪
♪ 空いっぱいの花火が 咲き誇る ♪
♪ Shimmering in your eyes ♪
♪ あなたの瞳に映り込んで ♪
♪ And spreading into a gentle sea of stars ♪
♪ やさしさとなって広がる 星の海 ♪
Lin Wanxing.
林晚星
You are really drunk.
本当に酔ってるな
♪ Every night ♪
♪ 毎晩 ♪
♪ I reach for starlight ♪
♪ 星の光に 手を伸ばす ♪
♪ Wandering through dreams with you ♪
♪ 君と夢の中を彷徨う ♪
We are the champions.
私たちはチャンピオン
♪ I follow the beat of my heart ♪
♪ 鼓動のリズムに乗せて ♪
♪ Like dust floating in the air ♪
♪ 宙を舞う塵のように ♪
♪ Because of your love ♪
♪ 君の愛が ♪
We are the champions.
私たちはチャンピオン
♪ I shine brilliantly ♪
♪ 私を輝かせる ♪
♪ I caught your eyes ♪
♪ 君のまなざしを見つけた ♪
♪ On the summer night ♪
♪ あの夏の夜に ♪
♪ Like stars that glow so bright ♪
♪ 眩しく輝く星のようだった ♪
♪ A spark in my heart ♪
♪ 胸に灯る小さな火は ♪
♪ Lost in a dream secretly ♪
♪ 夢の中へ そっと消えてゆく ♪
♪ With the evening breeze whispering in my ear ♪
♪ 夜風が耳元に 吹き寄せる告白 ♪
♪ Fireworks bloom across the sky ♪
♪ 空いっぱいの花火が 咲き誇る ♪
♪ Shimmering in your eyes ♪
♪ あなたの瞳に映り込んで ♪
♪ And spreading into a gentle sea of stars ♪
♪ やさしさとなって広がる 星の海 ♪
I'm going for a morning run.
朝のジョギングに行く
Drink some orange juice to sober up when you wake up.
起きたらジュースで酔いを覚ませ
Someone said "We are the champions" 18 times in her sleep.
寝言で18回も チャンピオンだって言ってたぞ
I've received your wish to win.
林先生の勝ちたい願いは受け取った
Working on it.
努力中だ
We all know who wasn't paying attention
あの時 誰が真面目じゃなかったか
at that time.
自分で分かってるわよね
But I never thought
でも思いもしなかった
that I could
まさかみんなと
make it to the finals with you guys.
決勝まで行けるなんて
I want to grandly thank
改めて盛大に感謝したい
Mr. Win once again.
ミスターウィンに
First bow.
一礼
-First bow. -Thank you, Coach.
- 一礼 - コーチありがとう
Second bow.
二礼
♪ Waiting for a dark cloud to pass by you ♪
♪ 一つの雲が君を過ぎる ♪
Besides your grandparents in this world,
この世界には祖父母以外にも
♪ Listen closely to its cries ♪
♪ その泣き声を聴いて ♪
there is someone else who loves you.
君を愛する人がいる
♪ The heavy rain will wash away your reflection ♪
♪ 大雨が君の面影をさらう ♪
♪ And carry it toward distant scenery ♪
♪ 遠くの景色へ ♪
[Photographer's Works]
[カメラマンの作品]
[Choose from Photos]
[スマホアルバムから選択]
[Photos and Videos]
[画像と動画]
[Change Cover]
[アルバムカバーを変更]
♪ Every experience has its meaning ♪
♪ すべての経験に意味がある ♪
[Superstar Slacker]
[干物見習い]
♪ Scene by scene, they come together to form who I am ♪
♪ 一つ一つが自分になる ♪
♪ Even the wounds that leave behind their marks ♪
♪ 傷跡さえも残しても ♪
[Permission Settings] [Friend Profile]
[権限][友達のプロフィール]
[Superstar Slacker]
[干物見習い]
Take this off.
これを外して
Thank you.
ありがとう
Okay, that works.
はい できた
Okay, one more turn.
よし もう一回り
Are you making this
これを作るのは
for yourself or as a gift?
自分用？それとも誰かに？
As a gift.
誰かに
This style represents the infinite continuation of feelings.
これは感情の無限の連続を意味する
Then this person
じゃあその人は
must be very close to you.
きっと仲が良いのね
Yes.
ええ
Thank you.
ありがとう
You're welcome. Take care.
どういたしまして 気をつけて
♪ The rainbow deep within your heart ♪
♪ 君の心の虹が ♪
♪ Soaring atop the peak ♪
♪ 頂点を駆け抜け ♪
♪ I'm right here by your side ♪
♪ 私がそばにいて ♪
♪ My heart beats in time with yours ♪
♪ 心も共に鼓動する ♪
♪ Through twists and daring adventures ♪
♪ 波乱と冒険が ♪
♪ I'll help you embrace your transformation ♪
♪ 君の成長を実現する ♪
♪ And guard all that makes you one of a kind ♪
♪ 君の特別を守る ♪
♪ It's my intuition ♪
♪ 私の直感 ♪
♪ We'll journey hand-in-hand into tomorrow ♪
♪ 一緒に未来へ ♪
♪ My heart remains true, bound in the name of love ♪
♪ 愛の名の下に真心は不変 ♪
♪ I cross the wild wasteland till you come into view ♪
♪ 君が現れるまで 荒野を越えて ♪
♪ Bringing me fiery courage ♪
♪ 情熱の勇気をくれて ♪
♪ And standing with me to overcome every trial ♪
♪ 数々の試練を 共に乗り越える ♪
♪ Till you burst into my world ♪
♪ 君が私の世界に 飛び込むまで ♪
♪ Side by side, we chase our shared dreams ♪
♪ 私たちの夢は並んで ♪
♪ I gaze into your resolute eyes ♪
♪ 君の力強い視線を見つめ ♪
♪ Marching forward to our shared tomorrow ♪
♪ 私たちの未来の明日へ ♪
♪ I'm waiting for you ♪
♪ 君を待っている ♪
♪ My heart remains true, bound in the name of love ♪
♪ 愛の名の下に真心は不変 ♪
♪ I cross the wild wasteland till you come into view ♪
♪ 君が現れるまで 荒野を越えて ♪
♪ Bringing me fiery courage ♪
♪ 情熱の勇気をくれて ♪
♪ And standing with me to overcome every trial ♪
♪ 数々の試練を 共に乗り越える ♪
♪ Till you burst into my world ♪
♪ 君が私の世界に 飛び込むまで ♪
♪ Side by side, we chase our shared dreams ♪
♪ 私たちの夢は並んで ♪
♪ I gaze into your resolute eyes ♪
♪ 君の力強い視線を見つめ ♪
♪ Marching forward to our shared tomorrow ♪
♪ 私たちの未来の明日へ ♪
♪ I'm waiting for you ♪
♪ 君を待っている ♪
You sing really well.
歌うまいね
Why don't you join our band as the lead singer?
バンドのボーカルをやらない？
I'll think about it.
考えてみる
Okay. Our next song is "Sunrise."
よし 次の曲は「日出」だ
-Great!
いいぞ
[Scholarly Progress]
[学業進歩]
Coach.
コーチ
[Final Tactical Analysis]
[決勝戦術分析]
Are we going to discuss
永川恒久への戦術を
the tactics against Yongchuan Hengjiu?
話し合うんですよね？
[Yongchuan Hengjiu's 4-1-4-1 Formation]
[永川恒久4141陣形]
Hengjiu's 4-1-4-1 formation.
恒久の4141陣形は
It consists of 4 defenders,
４人のディフェンダー
one defensive midfielder,
１人のボランチ
4 midfielders,
４人のミッドフィールダー
and one forward.
そして１人のフォワードだ
You're amazing.
さすがは大魔王だな
We just need to do our best anyway.
とにかく全力を尽くすだけだろ
Being the runner-up is fine.
準優勝でもいいじゃん
Right, Boss?
なあ 兄貴？
You are quick-witted.
お前頭いいだろ
What are the weaknesses of this formation?
この陣形の弱点は何だ？
Their defensive midfielder
彼らのボランチは
is the key to their passing routes.
パスコースの要だ
[Yongchuan Hengjiu's 4-1-4-1 Formation]
[永川恒久4141陣形]
But the forward is definitely Qin Qiechu.
フォワードは秦且初に違いないが
Who will be the defensive midfielder?
ボランチは誰だ？
It should be their captain, Fang Sulun.
キャプテンの方蘇倫だろう
I've checked Hengjiu's info.
恒久の資料を調べた
In this league,
今大会では
our focus
僕たちの注目は
has always been on their forward, Qin Qiechu.
ずっとＦＷの秦且初だったが
But actually, their captain's
実はキャプテンの実力も
strength shouldn't be underestimated either.
侮れないんだ
He personally scored 11 goals
彼は11得点し
and provided 18 effective assists.
18回のアシストを決めている
Right.
そう
Although he is not as fast as Qin Qiechu,
スピードは秦且初に劣るが
his ball control is solid
ボールキープ力は悪くない
and consistent.
しかも非常に安定している
Good analysis.
良い分析だ
You all look the part.
なかなか堂に入ってるな
Coach, how do we break it?
コーチ どう崩すんです？
[Yongchuan Hengjiu's 4-1-4-1 Formation]
[永川恒久4141陣形]
[Aggressive end-to-end football]
[強気の攻め合い]
-Aggressive end-to-end football.
強気の攻め合い？
How can we hold our own against Yongchuan Hengjiu in this attacking clash?
永川恒久に勝てるわけない
It's like bringing a knife to a gunfight.
綿で石を叩くようなもんだ
[Aggressive end-to-end football]
[強気の攻め合い]
[Distance covered by players]
[シーズン選手の走行距離]
Look.
ほら
Here is the comparison of the total distance covered by everyone.
これが君たちの走行距離の比較だ
Fu Xinshu.
付新書
[Wen Chengye] [Lin Lu] [Fu Xinshu]
[文成業][林鹿][付新書]
From 5,100 meters
元の5100メートルから
to 6,830 meters now.
今は6830メートルだ
You can now completely control the whole field.
もう完全にピッチを支配できる
[Distance covered by players]
[シーズン選手の走行距離]
Qin Ao.
秦敖
From 5,530 meters
元の5530メートルから
to 7,300 meters now.
今は7300メートルだ
[Qin Ao] [Chen Jianghe]
[秦敖][陳江河]
You are
君は
the strongest blade to tear through
相手のディフェンスを切り裂く
the opponent's defense.
最強の刃だ
There's another person who has completely transformed.
そして完全に 生まれ変わった者がいる
Lin Lu.
林鹿
The growth rate of your total distance covered
君の走行距離の増加率は
stands at 38%.
38パーセントだ
You are at a whole new level now.
もはや別次元のレベルだ
Numbers don't lie.
データは嘘をつかない
Every one of you
君たちは今 全員が
has become stronger than before.
以前より強くなっている
[Distance covered by players]
[シーズン選手の走行距離]
And more importantly,
そして更に重要なのは
you are more united now.
今の結束力だ
Although I never said it,
ずっと言わなかったが
whether you are sitting here
今こうして
loosely like this now
バラバラに座っていても
or on the field,
ピッチの上にいても
I can feel it very clearly
君たちが一つのチームだと
that you are a whole.
はっきりと感じている
With these numbers,
このデータを見て
do you still think you're bringing a knife to a gunfight?
まだ自分が綿だと思うか？
When I left the UK,
イギリスを離れた時
I was actually very lost.
実は私も迷っていた
I couldn't find the meaning of football for a while.
サッカーの意義が分からなくなった
I felt at that time
あの時は
that the youth training there was just a business,
ユース育成はただのビジネスで
a cruel business.
残酷なビジネスだと思っていた
But I had no choice.
だが仕方ない
This is the essence of competitive sports,
それが競技スポーツの本質だ
cruelness.
残酷なんだ
But now,
しかし今
I have found
君たちの中に
the meaning of football in you.
サッカーの意義を見つけた
Maybe you haven't realized it yourselves.
自分では気づいて いないかもしれないが
On your path to victory,
勝利への道において
you've long stopped being soft.
君たちはもう綿じゃない
Long stopped.
とっくに違うんだ
You yourselves
君たち自身が
are the meaning of football.
サッカーの意義なんだ
Head-to-head,
真っ向勝負だ
stone against stone.
石対石
Find Yongchuan Hengjiu's flaw,
永川恒久の弱点を見つけ
and then score the winning goal.
そしてトドメを刺す
Wait,
いや
is no one going to say anything?
誰も意見言わない？
Don't look at me. I can't be the first to speak.
見るな 俺は最初には言えない
If I do, my wise persona will be gone.
言ったら知的なキャラが崩れる
Wise?
知的？
Since when have you had a wise persona?
そんなキャラないだろ
I can't stand it anymore!
もう我慢できない
Let's do this!
やってやろうぜ
Lin Lu, we can't be runners-up again!
林鹿 もう準優勝はごめんだ
Right, we are the champions!
ああ 俺たちが優勝だ
Champions!
優勝だ
-We are the champions! -Champions!
- 俺たちが優勝だ - 優勝
-We must be the champions!
- 絶対に優勝だ
Let's go for training!
合宿へ出発
-Let's go.
- 行くぞ
Let's go.
行くぞ
-We must be the champions! -7,300 meters.
- 絶対に優勝だ - 7300メートル
[Lin Lu] [Chen Jianghe]
[林鹿][陳江河]
-Let's go. -Guys.
- 行くぞ - みんな
Watch me break through to 8 kilometers.
突破してやる ８キロまで突破するぞ
Let's go.
行くぞ
Let's practice the tactics we learned today.
今日の戦術を練習しておこう
You know what? This gym alone
知ってるか？ここのジム
is bigger than all 5 gyms I have at home combined.
俺の家の５倍は広いぞ
Also, also,
それから
the shower room inside
あの奥のシャワー室
is huge and smells good.
めちゃ広くて いい匂いがする
Also, well...
それにあの
the... the heated pool.
温水プールとか
Thank you, Coach!
コーチ ありがとう
Right, and the tactical meeting room over there.
あっちの戦術会議室も
It's all automated equipment,
全部自動化されてて
just like a spaceship in a movie!
映画の宇宙船みたいだ
-Also... -Yes.
- それに - ああ
There's central AC,
中央エアコンもあって
which far outperforms Ms. Lin's
林先生んちのトラクター エアコンより
-old AC! -Old AC.
- ずっといい - トラクターって
Right.
そうだ
Alright.
よし
Don't you want to play to your heart's content?
思い切り蹴りたいんだろ？
Go!
行け
No breakthrough.
突破してないぞ
0.1 seconds away from 8 seconds. Again.
８秒まであと0.1秒 もう一回
Press forward, press forward.
前へ押し上げろ
8.2 seconds.
8.2秒
Again.
もう一回
Go for it! You've got this!
頑張れ 頑張れ
8 seconds!
８秒
[Three days before the finals] [Yongchuan final field]
[試合の３日前 永川決勝会場]
Brothers,
みんな
I never expected
まさか決勝戦を
that we would still play the final here.
ここでやることになるとはな
It feels weird.
変な気分だ
What's weird?
どこがだよ
Get up where you fall.
転んだ場所から立ち上がるんだ
Brothers,
お前ら
let's enjoy this last match.
この最後の試合を楽しもうぜ
Ms. Lin.
林先生
Let's go.
行きましょう
No training today.
今日の練習はなしだ
Go back and rest.
戻って休め
The coach is right.
コーチの言う通りよ
Never be overly nervous before a match.
試合前に緊張しすぎないで
Otherwise, you might crack under pressure.
張り詰めた糸は切れやすいわ
However,
でも
everyone must be back before 9:00 PM.
９時前には 必ず戻ってくること
-Got it.
- 了解
No problem!
問題ないっす
-Let's go.
行こう
Only 3 bottles left!
３本しか残ってない
The stylish kind.
ちょっとかっこいい感じの
You've been ordering for so long.
ずっと選んでるけど
Are you done yet?
まだ決まらないのか
Still picking. Still picking.
まだ選んでるんだよ
Still ordering?
まだだよ
-I'll change to this one. -The earliest skin.
- こっちの店にする - 一番最初のスキン
This one is okay,
これ悪くないな
but delivery takes 2 hours.
配達に２時間もかかるぞ
Let's send a representative to go buy some.
代表が買いに行こう
-I won't go. -The earliest one.
- 俺は行かない - 一番最初のやつ
Then who will go?
じゃあ誰が？
And now it's updated to this.
それで今これが出て
But this one is the coolest right now.
でも今一番かっこいいのはこれだ
And it has a car skin.
車のスキンもある
-Stop hiding! It's you!
- 隠れるなよ - お前だ
-Boss! It's you! -It's you, Lu.
- 兄貴 お前だよ - 呼ばれてるぞ 鹿鹿
This is my bed.
ここは私のベッドだ
My bad, sorry.
悪い悪い ごめん
I'll make it for you.
ちゃんと片付けとくから
I want vanilla ice cream.
バニラアイス頼む
Okay, okay.
わかった わかった
Then I'll just go buy my mom
ちょうど母さんの
a birthday present.
誕生日プレゼントも買ってくるか
Let's go, Boss!
行こうぜ 兄貴
I don't want to go!
行きたくない
Go.
行け
-Go. Go. -Let's go.
- 早く行けよ - 行こう
I want chocolate one!
チョコ頼む
-I want blueberry one! -Taro!
- ブルーベリー - タロイモ
-I want strawberry one! -Vanilla one.
- イチゴ - バニラ
I'll wait for you.
待ってるぞ
-Okay. -I'll wait for you.
- ああ - 待ってるぞ
-Thank you.
- お疲れ様
I need to check quickly
早く確認しないと
to see if we missed anything.
漏れがないか
We might need to buy more later.
後で買い足す羽目になる
Boss, are you doing this on purpose?
兄貴 わざとだろ？
It's so heavy. Won't you help me share the load?
こんな重いのに少しは手伝えよ
What's the rush?
何焦ってんだ？
It's time to test the results of your workout.
鍛錬の成果を試す時が来たんだ
I just remembered a saying.
ある言葉を思い出したよ
You are the company you keep.
朱に交われば赤くなるってな
Boss, you've really been corrupted by Wen Chengye.
文成業のせいで性格悪くなったな
Let me tell you.
言っとくが
Playing football is about winning.
勝つためにサッカーしてんだ
Right?
だろ？
Think about how Qin Qiechu
秦且初が俺たちを見た
looked at us back then.
あの目つきを思い出せ
I just have to win.
絶対に勝って
I won't let him show off to me.
ギャフンと言わせてやる
And that captain Fang Sulun,
それにキャプテンの 方蘇倫とかいうやつ
always pretending to be a good guy.
毎日いい人ぶって
Why is he copying my persona?
付のキャラをパクりやがって
He's really...
確かにあいつだ
Unbelievable.
呆れるぜ
Speak of the devil.
噂をすれば影だな
What a coincidence.
奇遇だな
[Yuan Yuan Vintage] [Specialist Pre-Owned Luxury Boutique]
[源源中古 中古ブランド専門店]
Specialist Pre-Owned Luxury Boutique.
中古ブランド専門店
What is it?
何する店だ？
I heard things are much cheaper in this kind of shop.
中古はすごく安いらしいって
Let's go pick a good one for my mom.
母さんにいいのを選ぼう
-Let's go.
- 行こう
Welcome.
いらっしゃいませ
Feel free to look around.
ご自由にご覧ください
Hello.
こんにちは
This ring is too expensive.
この指輪 高すぎるだろ
Wait.
いや
Where did you get so much money?
お前どこにそんな金があるんだ？
Boss, I saved my pocket money for a year,
１年貯めたお小遣いだよ
and it's all gone.
すっからかんだ
So filial, Lu.
親思いだな 鹿鹿
You have no idea.
お前分かってないな
I'm tanned like a piece of coal now.
今石炭みたいに黒焼けだろ
As soon as I get home, my mom will definitely throw a huge fit.
家に帰ったら母さんが大騒ぎする
To shut her up,
黙らせるために
since her birthday is coming soon,
もうすぐ誕生日だから
I bought her a ring to coax her.
指輪を買って機嫌を取るんだよ
You're getting as smart as I am.
俺みたいに賢くなったな
But honestly,
でも言わせてもらうと
this ring is really pretty.
この指輪 本当に綺麗だ
It really is pretty.
確かに綺麗だ
But what I don't understand
でもよく分からないのが
is how you spent so much time...
お前はどうやってそんな長時間
[Basic Activity Organization] [Alternative Forecasts]
[基本活動の組織] [選択可能な予測]
[Football Team Training Record Progress Schedule]
[サッカー部練習記録進捗表]
Three days left.
あと３日
Who is it?
誰？
Coming.
今行く
Li,
礼ちゃん
why are you here?
どうしてここに？
I'm here to cheer you and the kids on.
あなたと子供たちを応援しに来たの
I also brought you this,
これも持ってきたわ
your favorite milk tea.
あなたの好きなミルクティー
Thanks.
ありがとう
30% sugar, right?
砂糖３割よね？
So,
どう？
the competition is in 3 days.
試合まであと３日だけど
Are you nervous?
緊張してる？
Of course, I'm nervous.
もちろん緊張してるわ
Much more nervous than I was sitting my college entrance exams.
自分の大学入試の時よりずっとね
It'll be fine.
大丈夫よ
Our Wanxing will be fine.
うちの星なら問題ないわ
Just believe in yourself and be yourself.
自分を信じて 自分らしくいればいいの
Your outfit
その服
looks way cooler than that in your videos.
動画の時よりずっとかっこいいね
You watched our band's videos?
私たちのバンドの動画見たの？
How is it? Not bad, right?
どう？悪くないでしょ
Right now, we have
今だいたい
about 73 followers.
73人のファンがいるの
73?
73人
There's still a little gap before becoming internet famous.
インフルエンサーには まだ少し遠いわね
We just started the account.
アカウント開設したばかりだし
Having 73 is pretty good.
73人なら上出来よ
And we also got our first commercial gig.
初めての営業の仕事も入ったの
Getting a commercial gig with just 73 followers?
73人で営業が取れるなんて
That's impressive.
すごいね
It's just that the time of the first gig
ただ その初めての営業の時間が
clashes with the match.
試合の時間と被っちゃって
So I probably won't be able to go
だからその日は
and cheer for you guys in person that day.
応援に行けないかも
Did you come to me
もしかして罪悪感で
just because you feel guilty, didn't you?
私に会いに来たの？
No way.
違うわよ
I came...
私はただ
just because I wanted to see you.
あなたに会いたかったの
The other day,
あの日
I made this myself, and...
これを自分で作って
I just wanted to give it to you.
あなたにプレゼントしたくて
You're too kind.
気を遣わないで
Look.
ほら
Do you like it?
気に入った？
It's really pretty.
すごく綺麗
Thank you.
ありがとう
On my way here, I saw
来る途中で
someone selling these.
これを売ってるのを見て
I thought they would suit me.
私に似合うと思って
Can you help me put them on?
つけてくれる？
No problem.
いいわよ
Let's go to the bathroom.
トイレに行こう
All done.
できた
After those kids graduate,
あの子たちが卒業したら
have you thought about what you want to do?
次は何をするか考えてるの？
Not yet.
まだ決めてない
I'll wait until they graduate.
卒業してから考えるわ
Right now, I just want to do my best
今はただ全力を尽くして
to give them a result with no regrets.
悔いのない結果を残してあげたい
What about you?
あなたは？
Me?
私はね
Actually, I came back to the country this time
実は今回帰国したのは
for a friend.
ある友達のためなの
She was in a tough spot back then
彼女はその時困難に陥って
and almost desperate.
絶望しかけていた
I thought,
私は思ったの
if I came back,
私が帰国すれば
I could be with her
彼女に寄り添って
and help her out of the haze.
陰から救い出せるって
But when I actually came back, I found that
でも実際に帰ってきて気づいたの
she was much stronger than I thought.
彼女は私が思うより強かった
Whether I'm there or not,
私がいなくても
her smile is bright enough.
彼女の笑顔は十分に輝いていたわ
Thank you,
ありがとう
Li.
礼ちゃん
Seal
封印
lifted.
解除
Lu,
鹿
what are you doing?
何してるのか？
Drinking so much water.
水ばかり飲んで
You wanna use the bathroom during training
練習中にトイレ行って
and slack off, right?
サボる気でしょ
I'm just thirsty.
喉が渇いただけだ
And I want to wet my whistle, okay?
喉を潤してるんだよ
Just let him go.
許してやれよ
Every night,
毎晩
he yells about beating Yongchuan Hengjiu.
永川恒久を倒すって騒いでるんだ
Who else would be thirsty?
そりゃ喉も渇くだろ
Don't say that, Boss.
兄貴 お前もだろ
If you hadn't forced me to watch the game in the middle of the night,
夜中に無理やり試合を見せなきゃ
I wouldn't have dreamed about Hengjiu.
恒久の夢なんか見なかったぞ
You dreamed about the game?
試合の夢を見たのか？
How was it?
結果はどうだった？
Did we win? Tell me.
勝ったのか 早く言え
I didn't dream about the result,
結果は見てないけど
but
その代わり
I dreamed of Fang Sulun's big face.
方蘇倫のデカい顔を見て
Then I was scared awake.
びっくりして起きた
Look at you.
情けない
Let's go.
行くぞ
To training.
練習だ
Hurry up.
早く
What's the rush?
何をそんなに急いでるんだよ
The last one there is a loser.
ビリは負けだ
[Hongjing No. 8 High's Dressing Room]
[宏景八高チームロッカールーム]
[Yongchuan Provincial Youth Super League]
[永川省ユーススーパーリーグ]
Come on, hurry!
頑張れ 頑張れ 早く
[Hongjing No. 8 High School versus Yongchuan Hengjiu]
[宏景八高 ＶＳ 永川恒久]
Come on, speed up!
ほら スピード上げろ
Come on, go for it.
頑張れ 頑張れ
Qi Liang, mind your arms!
祁亮 腕の振りに注意だ
Okay, okay.
はい はい わかりました
Come on, go for it.
頑張れ 頑張れ
What's wrong?
どうした？
Come on.
ほら
Did you sprain it?
足首を捻ったか？
I'm fine.
大丈夫だ
A little bit.
少し痛いだけ
It just hurts a little bit.
ほんの少し痛いだけで
Endure it.
我慢しろ
How is it?
どうだ？
A little.
少しだけ
Go back and rest.
戻って休め
Ice it for 15 minutes at the hotel.
ホテルで15分冷やせ
I'm fine, Coach.
平気です コーチ
I can still train.
まだ練習できます
Go back and rest.
戻って休め
Don't risk a big loss for a small gain.
小事で大事を失うな
Who shares a room with him?
こいつと同室は誰だ？
Me.
俺です
Coach, the match is tomorrow.
コーチ 明日が試合です
Because the match is tomorrow,
明日が試合だからこそだ
this training isn't important.
重要なのはこの練習じゃない
Take him back.
送っていけ
Come on.
ほら
Let's go, Boss.
行こうぜ 兄貴
Let me do it. Let me.
俺がやる 俺がやる
-Be careful.
- ゆっくり
It's fine.
大丈夫だ
Others continue.
他の者は続けろ
How long will this take?
いつまで歩くんだよ
Let me carry you, come on.
おんぶしてやるよ ほら
You carry me?
お前が？
Speed up! Speed up!
スピードアップだ
The match is coming soon.
すぐ試合なんだぞ
If you get hurt, I can't afford to compensate you.
落とされたら弁償できないぞ
Be careful!
気をつけろよ
Don't be like Qin Ao.
秦敖みたいになるな
Chen!
陳
-Come on. -What's wrong?
- ほらほら - どうした？
Boss sprained his ankle.
兄貴が足を捻って
You should help me take him back to the hotel.
一緒にホテルへ送ってくれ
Okay. Let's go.
よし 行こう
Are you okay?
大したことないよな？
What could be wrong?
大したことないさ
Coach just won't let me practice.
コーチが練習を止めさせたんだ
It's not a big deal today, but
傷は浅いけど
the main thing is the match tomorrow.
明日が試合だからな
You should be more careful.
気をつけろよ
What could happen to a tough guy like me?
男なら平気だろ
Yeah, but you must be careful.
平気でも注意しろよ
Be careful.
ゆっくり ゆっくり
It's fine.
大丈夫だ
Are you sure you don't want to go to the hospital
病院行かなくていいのか？
and get some medicine or something?
薬とかもらわなくて？
It's just a minor injury.
かすり傷だ
It'll heal faster that way.
病院の方が早く治るぞ
I'm a tough guy.
男だろ
Stop pretending.
強がるなよ
Go back and apply ice immediately.
帰ってすぐ冷やすぞ
Then I'll get you some anti-inflammatory medicine.
炎症止めを取ってくる
-Okay. -It's just that…
- ああ - でもすぐ
the match is coming soon.
試合なんだし
Be a little more careful.
少しは気をつけろ
Even injured, I can still beat them.
怪我しても勝ってやるさ
Would it kill you not to pretend?
強がらないと死ぬのか？
Boss, do you have the room key?
兄貴 カード持ってるか？
No, I gave it to you.
いや お前に渡したぞ
-Look for it. -I put it right here.
- 探してくれ - ここに置いたのに
I don't have it.
ないぞ
Fang Sulun, what are you doing in our room?
方蘇倫 俺たちの部屋で何してる？
Don't go!
行くな
-I'll go! -Catch him!
- 俺が行く - 捕まえろ
-Okay, no problem! -I'll go to the elevator,
- わかった - エレベーターに行くぞ
-Lu! -I'll go with you!
- 鹿 - 俺も行く
Stop right there!
そこに立て
Brothers, hurry back.
みんな 早く戻ってきて
Our room got broken into. Hurry.
部屋に入られた 早く
Stop right there!
止まれ
Where do you think you’re going?
なぜ逃げる？
Wait a minute!
待て
You can run, but you can't hide.
逃げ切れると思うなよ
Wait for us to catch you at Hengjiu?
恒久まで捕まえに行くぞ
Confess, and you'll be treated leniently.
正直に話せば寛大に処す
Resist, and you'll be punished severely.
隠せば厳罰だ
Tell the truth, what were you doing in our room?
俺たちの部屋で何をしてたんだ？
Why do we need an explanation?
何の釈明だ
Ms. Lin,
林先生
report him directly.
告発しよう
Did Hengjiu send him to check out our tactics?
恒久が戦術を盗みに来させたんだろ
Yes, report him directly
そうだ すぐ告発だ
and disqualify him from the match.
出場資格を剥奪してやる
Did he really come
彼は本当に
to see our tactics?
戦術を見に来たのかな
Are you stupid?
バカか
They are Yongchuan Hengjiu.
相手は永川恒久だぞ
Why would they care about our tactics?
俺たちの戦術なんか見ないだろ
Can you hurry
早くしろよ
and just say something?
言えないのか？
If you don't, I'll report you directly.
言わないなら すぐ告発するぞ
-Don't! -What are you doing?
- 待って - 何をする
Let go!
手を離せ
-Let them handle it themselves. -Let go!
- 彼らに任せよう - 離せ
Let go! Stop! What do you want?
- 取るな 何をする
Lin Lu.
林鹿
Isn't this the ring you bought for your mom?
これ お母さんに買った指輪だろ？
Call the police.
警察を呼んでくれ
I-I took the ring.
この指輪は私が盗みました
But this is my own doing.
でも 個人的な犯行です
I don't want it to affect my team.
チームに迷惑はかけたくありません
This is my mom's ring.
これは母の指輪なんです
Lin Lu bought the ring for his mom.
これは林鹿が母親に買った指輪だぞ
How did it become your mom's?
なぜお前の母親のになる
This ring
この指輪は
was a birthday present
私が８歳の時
my dad bought my mom when I was 8.
父が母に買った 誕生日プレゼントです
Then why was it in the store?
じゃあなんで店にあったんだよ？
Did it fly there?
自分で飛んでいったとでも？
Because my mom passed away.
母が亡くなったからです
What are you talking about?
わけがわからない
Make it clear.
ちゃんと説明しろ
Three months after my mom died,
母が亡くなって３ヶ月後
my dad remarried.
父は再婚しました
The stepmother didn't like me.
継母は私を嫌っていて
She thought
彼女は
I was a third wheel in their marriage.
私が２人の邪魔をしてると 思ったんです
So my dad
だから父は私を
sent me to Hengjiu boarding school.
恒久の寄宿学校に入れました
I carried this ring
この指輪は
with me every day.
毎日身に着けていました
But when I went to boarding school, I was afraid of losing it,
でも寄宿学校でなくすのが怖くて
so I locked it in the cabinet at home.
家の棚にずっとしまっていたんです
But she must have found it.
でも継母に見つかったみたいで
She thought it was bad luck because it was my mom's
母の遺品は縁起が悪いと
and sold it.
売られてしまったんです
Later, my dad and I
その後 父と
had a fight over it.
このことでケンカになりました
I pieced together the torn receipt
破られた控えを貼り合わせて
to find the pre-owned luxury boutique.
やっとその中古品店を 見つけたんです
But I didn't expect
でも思わなかった
the price...
値段が...
So you got anxious.
それで焦ったのか
I've been working to earn money
ずっとバイトで稼いで
to buy it back.
買い戻そうと思ってたんです
But I didn't expect
でも まさか昨日
that you two bought it yesterday.
お２人に買われるなんて
When I saw you bought it,
あなたが買って行くのを見て
I don't know what happened to me.
自分でもどうかしてて
I just went crazy.
気が狂ったみたいでした
I only knew this ring
私には ただ この指輪を
had to stay with me.
手元に置かないとダメだったんです
But I was desperate.
でもパニックになって
I was wrong about this.
私が間違っていました
Lin Lu,
林鹿
I will return the money for the ring to you.
指輪のお金は返します
I will give you all my savings.
貯金は全部渡します
If it's not enough, I'll write you an IOU.
足りなければ借用書を書きます
I'm sorry, Lin Lu.
すみません 林鹿
This is the only thing
これは母が
my mom left me.
私に残してくれた唯一の物なんです
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
I can accept any punishment.
どんな罰でも受けます
I can also drop out.
コンテストも辞退します
But I don't want my own business
でも私のせいで
to affect Hengjiu.
恒久に迷惑はかけたくありません
Do you have anything else to ask?
他に何か質問はあるか
You guys decide this matter yourselves.
この件はあなたたちで決めて